让我们继续菲尔和戴安的故事吧
Let's get back to Phil and Diane.
菲尔找工作找得很辛苦
Phil's been having a hard time finding work,
而戴安想和他聊聊
and Diane wants him to talk to her
排解一下他的恐惧和失望
about his fear, his disappointment.
但是菲尔希望戴安相信他
And Phil wants Diane to trust him
相信他们能度过这个难关
that they'll get through this,
犯不着没完没了的互诉衷肠
ideally, without having to keep discussing feelings.
我理解的大意没错吧
Not your exact words, but am I wrong?
大多数男人都这个样
And most guys out there are the same way,
而女人们呢  如果你感到沮丧
but ladies, if you're feeling frustrated,
记着  这不是我们男人的错
remember, it's not our fault.
我们从小就被教育要坚强  而不是情绪化
We were raised to be strong, not emotional,
要拒绝软弱无能  而不是破罐破摔
to deny vulnerability, not embrace it.
你知道那会怎么样吗
And do you know what that makes us?
我们就过时了
Dinosaurs.
没人需要我们猎食
Nobody needs us to hunt wild animals for food.
也不需要我们砍树造屋
Nobody needs us to cut down trees to build shelter.
她们需要我们进化  赶上时代
They need us to evolve, to catch up.
自上世纪60年代起  女性角色发生了根本改变
Since the 1960s, women's roles have shifted radically.
随着她们...她们社会地位的改变
And as--uh, as their-- in--as their roles have changed,
那么女人们  她们...
so have women, they've-- they've, uh,
她们更加坚强了
well, they've become tougher,
对我们的要求更高了
and more demanding of us.
她们是搭档
They're partners.
谁  能怪她们呢  谁能...
And--and--who can blame them? Who--who can--
谁能...
who can, uh...
希望我们...
expecting us to...
去做...
to do this...
乔  乔
Joe! Joe!
乔
Joe!
Joe.
叫救护车
We need an ambulance.
总监：
zlean
你要吗
You want?
不用了
I'm good.
你已经基本痊愈了
Your limp's almost gone.
抱歉打断同事间的打情骂俏
It pains me to interrupt the collegial banter.
可要让我继续听下去就更抱歉了
It pains me even more to listen to it continue.
38岁  男性
38-year-old man.
在演讲时突然发烧  之后晕厥
Spikes a fever and collapses during a speaking engagement.
急诊室检查了血容量
E.R. checks out blood volume,
心功能  神经反射  都未见异常
cardiac function, and autonomic reflexes, all normal.
病人依靠告诉男人更娘炮一点来养家糊口
Patient makes a living telling men to behave more like women.
你竟然没有作出精神症状的鉴别诊断
I'm surprised you didn't throw psych symptoms
真新鲜
into the differential.
不管怎样  可能是脑动静脉畸形
Either way, could be a cerebral AVM.
急诊室已进行过头颅CT
E.R. did a head CT.
未见脑动静脉畸形征象
No sign of AVM.
但是个不错的想法
Decent thought, though.
那病人的哲理有点道理
The patient's philosophy makes perfect sense.
唯一的漏洞就是  那是不可能的
Its only flaw is that it's impossible.
物种可不会那样进化
Evolution does not work that way.
你不能就鱼谈论腿
You can't talk legs onto a fish.
我们终究会灭绝
We're gonna go extinct,
但我们是边喝威士忌边开超级跑车地灭绝
and we're gonna do it drinking scotch and driving muscle cars.
我说的对吧
Am I right?
我...  谢谢
Am I-- Thank you.
头部肌纤维发育不良呢
Cephalic fibromuscular dysplasia?
解释不了发烧
It doesn't explain the fever.
病人是在谈论妥协
The patient's talking about compromise.
如果你认为那是不可能的
If you don't think that's possible,
那你就是认为恋爱关系是不可能的
you don't think relationships are possible.
这屋里的  有人不同意这个观点吗
Anyone in this room in a position to disprove that?
这家伙就是在忽悠他的听众
This guy's just playing to his audience.
目前为止  女性是"自立"产业
Women are, by far, the biggest consumers
最庞大的顾客群体
of the "self-help" industry.
他可能有肺栓塞
He could have a pulmonary embolism.
肺内血栓增加了右心室后负荷
Clot in his lung increases right ventricular afterload,
导致脑血流减少
drops the blood flow to his brain.
应该做个肺动脉造影
We should do a pulmonary angiogram.
患者无肺栓塞常见的危险因素
Patient lacks major risk factors for a P.E.
当然还不能排除  但不是很像
Doesn't rule it out, just makes it unlikely.
先查个D-二聚体吧
Maybe we start with a D-dimer?
先不作造影这个侵入性检查
Less invasive than the angiogram.
好主意
Good idea.
好吧
Fine.
其实  我是来上大号的
Now, I am hereby searching for a number two.
我吃了不少粗粮
So I'm eating a lot of bran.
还有  我要一个领队的
Also, I want a team leader.
饰演福曼的旧角色
Someone to fill Foreman's old job.
为什么
Why?
你说得对  我们不需要更多的人事结构了
You're right. We don't need any more structure.
又不是说在这里有人差点被扎死
It's not like we had a near-fatal stabbing.
这不是那位乌克兰娇妻嘛
Well, if it isn't the old ball and Ukraine.
那是谁
Who's that?
他老婆
His wife.
-多米尼卡  -豪斯
- Dominika. - House.
你从监狱里熬出来了
You survived prison.
你也从大西洋城熬过来了
And you Atlantic City,
那里也有闹事者和监狱酒
where they also have gangs and pruno,
不过少那么一点累犯
but slightly less recidivism.
我在做乌克兰食品的运输生意
I start Ukrainian food truck business.
赌性一尽  大家都想来点克尼什薄面卷
After gambling--win, lose-- everybody likes a little knish.
你人在这里  而我好像记得我扔了
You're here, and I seem to remember throwing out
不少移民局寄来的认证信件
a bunch of certified letters from Immigration.
两者应该有关系
I'm assuming there's a connection.
我们的绿卡面试在四天后
Our green card interview is in four days.
他们来我们的公寓
They come to the apartment.
问我们的婚姻情况
They ask questions about marriage,
假期情况  家庭史
vacations, family history,
谁睡床的哪一边
what side of the bed each sleep on.
我们从不度假
We've never taken a vacation.
我不喜欢的你的家人  不喜欢男上女下
I don't like your family, and on top.
我听说基辅每年这时候最漂亮
I hear Kiev is lovely this time of year.
还有你妈妈  死了或者没死
And your mother, who may or may not be dead,
就我所知  还是很想念你的
for all I know, misses you.
会不会是天才医生害怕面对
Can it be that genius doctor is afraid to take on
小小的政府官僚呢
a silly government apparatchik?
我本想说我不是害怕而是不感兴趣
Well, I would say more not interested than afraid,
但有什么好争的
but why quibble?
那我就执行第二套计划
Then I go to plan "B."
给你一个你无法拒绝的提议
Make you an offer that cannot be refused.
你举办这种宣讲会有多久了
How long you been doing seminars?
婚姻咨询会  就这几年的事
The marriage counseling, just, uh, the past couple years.
那之前  我是个合作教练
Before that, I did corporate coaching.
无法想象你同样的建议
Can't imagine the same advice
对两个不同的听众群体都管用
works for both audiences.
我猜你是跟着市场走吧
Guess you shifted with the market?
我丈夫并不见利忘义  我们...
There's nothing cynical about my husband. He and I--
没事的  我明白
No, it's okay. I get it.
什么男人会认为男人应该更像女人一点呢
What guy thinks men should be more like women?
在密尔沃基的一间体育酒吧外
A macho jerk who got a big wake-up call
三个痛揍了我一顿的醉汉
courtesy of three drunks who beat the crap outta me
让我这个大男子主义的混蛋如梦初醒
outside a sports bar in Milwaukee.
我想这倒是解释了你病史上
I'm guessing that explains the broken wrist
手腕骨折这一条
in your medical history?
这三个白痴帮了我这辈子最大的一个忙
Those morons did me the biggest favor of my life.
我意识到
I realized I'd sacrificed my health
就为争论橄榄球问题  我不作退让
because I couldn't back down
根本就是在牺牲性命
from an argument over football.
遇见玛琳是我解开迷惑的最后一块拼图
Meeting Marlene was the final piece in the puzzle.
她改变了我的事业  我的饮食习惯
She changed my career, my diet.
她给了我人生的新方向
She gave me a whole new direction in life.
我们需要知道你具体是怎么改变饮食习惯的
We'll need to know exactly how you changed your diet,
还有改变的时间
and when.
把我公寓钥匙还我
Need my apartment key back.
如果你要跟我分手
If you're breaking up with me,
至少先跟我谈谈吧
can we at least talk about it first?
谁叫你只碎碎念却不跟我滚床单
Maybe if you weren't all nag and no shag.
我不和已婚男子上床
I don't sleep with married men.
回头我再配把钥匙
I'll get a copy made.
你才出狱
You're an ex-con.
如果你被发现向国家安全部作伪证
If you get caught perjuring yourself to homeland security,
就会被扔回监狱
you'll end up back in jail.
所以只要有丝毫
And that would be troubling
我们被发现的可能  就很麻烦
if there was the slightest chance that we'd get caught.
你们几乎互不相识
You barely know each other.
而你只有大约五分钟时间
You've got about five minutes
重塑自我变身已婚人士还要令人信服
to remake yourselves into a convincing married couple.
还有  这是为什么呢
And why?
多米尼卡能弄到张绿卡  你有什么好处
Dominika gets a green card. What's in this for you?
这就是假装爱上某个女人的男人会做的事
This is what men do for the women they pretend to love.
还有  如果通过了  她会给我三万块
Also, she's paying me 30,000 bucks once we pass.
显然克尼什薄面卷很好卖啊
Apparently knishes sell like hotcakes.
检验结果
Lab results.
我得等会才能再听你唠叨了
Afraid you're gonna have to finish your nag later.
我说过我觉得这很傻吧
I said I think it's stupid, right?
那没其它好说的了
Then I think I'm done.
D-二聚体正常  肺栓塞可排除
D-dimer came back normal. Rules out pulmonary embolism.
我们的病人是真心相信
And our patient's a true believer
大男子主义的愚蠢
about the follies of masculinity.
他在三年前经历了一次精神洗礼
He underwent a spiritual overhaul three years ago.
之后便不再吃麸质和红肉
He also went off gluten and red meat.
可惜  这些都解释不了他的症状
Unfortunately, that doesn't explain any of his symptoms.
他的举动还真是"一点"不荒唐啊
One of those points is not absurd.
改变自己的想法有什么荒唐的
What's absurd about a change of heart?
他的新理念让他变成一个更好的人
What this guy believes is making him a better person.
他在克制自己最基本的本能
He's going against his baser instincts.
"基本"意味着最基础的
"Base" meaning foundational,
是人天生就该做的事情
meaning things we are biologically programmed to do.
不做该做的事还真是自然而然啊
Yes, perfectly natural that he stopped doing that stuff.
就是这种心态
You know, that's the kind of lapse
会阻碍你成为队伍领袖的
that could take you out of the running for team leader.
好奇怪啊  我一点都不在乎
I feel surprisingly okay with that.
周薪会涨50块噢
Comes with a 50-buck-a-week raise.
我参选
I'm in.
你会后悔的
You don't want to do that.
你要有放弃自尊的准备
Might need your dignity later in life.
你就不必了
You didn't.
这样她可就要如愿以偿了
And she could be on her way to living the dream
除非你们都奋起...
unless the rest of you nut up and give her--
他的精神洗礼
This spiritual overhaul...
是不是出现在一次身体病变后
Did it come after a physical overhaul?
某种大创伤
A major injury of some kind?
酒吧斗殴
Bar fight.
-但骨折的手腕也解释不了  -亚当斯  跟我来
- But there's no way a broken wrist explains-- -Adams, come with me.
你俩都来
You too.
至于你们
You guys...
再去复刻一把
Get a copy of that made.
那些家伙是不是把你的小弟当球踢啊
Did those dudes bend your ball sack like Beckham?
三年前  酒吧斗殴
Three years ago. The bar fight.
这是豪斯医生  他有个理论
This is Dr. House. He has a theory.
亚当斯医生  帮我捡一下
Oh, Dr. Adams, would you mind?
我问了个问题  你应该能回答吧
I asked you a question. I assume you know the answer.
是的  我的腹股沟被膝盖顶了好几下
Yeah, I took a couple serious knees to the groin.
我这是怎么了
What has gotten into me?
奇斯医生
Dr. Chase.
捡起来就是了
Just pick it up.
你知道我到底怎么了吗
Do you know what's wrong with me?
你的问题
Nothing that "The Golden Girls"
交给"黄金女孩"  肯定立马解决
couldn't have handled in 23 hilarious minutes.
更年期综合症
You had a hot flash.
那帮人踢你的小弟
Those guys kicked your guys
踢得太重  造成了持久性损害
hard enough to do lasting damage.
你面前明明有两个
You didn't even look when presented
相当性感的臀部  你却视而不见
with two reasonably attractive tuchi.
我说了  怎么着吧
Yeah, I said it!
我是在听你说话
I was listening to my doctor.
人们通常用耳朵来听
People generally listen with their ears,
留着眼睛到处瞎看
leaving their eyes free to wander.
我猜你的睾酮水平
I'm guessing that your testosterone level
比比伯还低
is just below "Bieber."
作抽血化验以确认
Do a blood test to confirm,
再开始激素替代治疗
and start hormone replacement.
难怪你认为女性是如此的伟大
It's no wonder that you think women are so great.
你过去三年基本上就是个女人
You've basically been one for the last three years.
化验结果证明豪斯是对的
Tests confirm House is right.
低睾酮能解释你的所有症状
Low testosterone explains all your symptoms.
在替代治疗后  应该都会好转
They should go away with replacement therapy.
我们会先用大剂量
We're gonna give you a fairly high dose.
在你生理功能恢复后  再逐渐减量
Over time, your personal physician may reduce it a little.
麻烦你转个身
Just need you to turn around.
这会增加他的性欲吗
Will the shots increase his libido?
你担心这个问题吗
Are you worried about that?
不是
No.
-是不是我没能满足你  -不是的  只是...
- Have you been unsatisfied? - No. No, it's just...
一直都是我主动
Well, it's usually me that initiates things.
有时...
Sometimes I...
我以为你并不是很爱我
I think maybe you aren't that attracted to me.
说什么胡话啊
Are you crazy?
注射后  你会发现性欲增强
With these injections, you will see an increase in sex drive.
好的  很好
Okay, great.
-打完了  -好的
- All done. - Okay.
事情不太对劲
Oh, something's wrong.
我好像尿裤子了
I think I peed myself.
这是睾酮引起的吗
Is that from the testosterone?
不可能
It couldn't be.
我想你还不能出院回家
I don't think you're going home just yet.
膀胱并没有问题
It's not a plumbing problem.
也就是说是神经性的
Means it's probably neurological.
然后呢
And?
说出多米尼卡三个兄弟的名字
And name Dominika's three brothers.
弗拉基米尔  季莫申科  还有...
Volodymyr, Oleksiy, and...
低睾酮并不是症状之一
Low testosterone is off the table as a symptom.
他三年前被踢了小弟弟
Guy got his nuts cracked three years ago.
不需要再往前追溯了
Don't need to look much further than that.
难道他只是碰巧
So his hose just happens to spring a leak
在住院时  因毫不相关的病
at the same time he's in a hospital
而随地小便吗
for a totally unrelated problem.
费奥多尔
Fjodor.
是费帝尔
It's Fedir.
如果低睾酮
If low testosterone means
能让我免受其它疾病
I can't get sick with something else,
谁赶紧踢我一脚
then punch me in the junk right now.
要不是我嫌麻烦  我肯定踢
I would, if it weren't redundant.
费帝尔是跟米科拉结婚的那个吗
Is Fedir the one who married Mykola?
米科拉是多米尼卡的叔叔
Mykola is Dominika's uncle.
为何你能记住我们的
How is it you can retain every detail
每个习惯和生活细节
of our habits and personal lives,
却记不住这些
and none of this?
因为我发现  没意思的事情
'Cause I find it hard to remember things
我完全记不住
I don't give a crap about.
我只知道  多米尼卡有个兄弟  叫某某
Here go, Dominika has one brother, and his name is al.
也许睾丸损伤使他易发其它疾病
Maybe the testicular damage set the stage for something worse.
多发性硬化可导致尿失禁
Multiple sclerosis causes incontinence,
而低睾酮水平的男性  病情加重得更快
and progresses faster in men with low T.
一针见血
Way to stay on point.
这种领导能力
It's that kind of leadership
能让你从众人中脱颖而出
that's putting you at the head of the pack.
哪来的众人  只有她一个人申请
There is no pack. She's the only applicant.
那就这么定了
Well, that's settled, then.
让你的下属去做腰穿
Have your underlings do an LP
以及头颅和脊髓的MRI
and get a cranio-spinal MRI
排查有无多发性硬化相关的迹象
to check for plaques associated with M.S.
我去通知福曼  你晋升了
I will go tell Foreman about your promotion.
等下
Wait.
本来除了我  没人在乎这个头衔
So nobody cares about the job till I apply,
结果突然又变成了限量版的抢手货
and suddenly it's the last limited-edition lightsaber at comic-con.
只是觉得  这个职位应该给...
Just seems like it should go to someone with more...
更资深的人
Seniority.
也就是你
Meaning you.
我是说"更"  不是"最"
I said "More," not "Most."
就是说你或陶博
Meaning you or Taub.
豪斯是个独裁者
House is a dictator.
二把手只是个虚职
Second in command is a meaningless position.
放在简历上总归是好看的
Doesn't look meaningless on my resume.
不一定就会是虚职啊
Doesn't have to be meaningless at all.
在合适的人手里  会变得有意义
The right person could turn it into something.
让部门运行得更顺畅
Get the department running smoothly.
我真好奇这"合适的人"是谁
I wonder who that "Right person" could be.
豪斯是部门主管
House is the head of the department.
只有让女性
It's only fair that a woman
当另一名主管  才公平
should hold the other position of authority.
好啊  那就让平等来得更彻底一些吧
Yeah, let's go affirmative action on this,
那我就赢定了
because then I'll definitely win.
这正是豪斯的目的
This is what House wants.
哄骗我们  看我们为空头衔抢得头破血流
Wind us up and watch us fight over an empty title,
考虑到前段时间发生的事情
which would make us extra stupid
这只会让我们显得更蠢
because of what we've just been through.
我们应该让他来选  然后忘了这事
We should let him choose whoever he wants and move on.
如果我的脑脊液里有蛋白质
So if these proteins are in my spinal fluid,
是不是就得了多发性硬化
that means I have M.S.?
蛋白质说明有多发性硬化的可能
Proteins may indicate M.S.
这种病没有检查可以确诊
There's no one definitive test.
所以豪斯医生还让你做MRI
That's why Dr. House ordered an MRI as well.
这是麻醉剂
This is anesthetic.
这个诊断确实挺吓人
It's a scary diagnosis.
但医学在进步
But advances are being made.
今年就又有几种药问世
Several drugs approved just this year.
实话实说  现在
To be honest, at the moment,
我更担心
I'm feeling a little more worried
注射的睾酮素
about the testosterone injections.
让我觉得有点...怪怪的
It's making me feel, uh, different.
有点兴奋
Just kind of amped.
我经历了人生的巨大转折
I went through this big life change,
而且觉得这个转折十分...
and it felt really...
有意义
Meaningful.
但如果它们都只是因为激素有问题呢
But what if it was all just chemistry?
缺少睾酮素可能是因素之一
Loss of testosterone could have been a factor,
但不妨把它看作是催化剂
but think of it as a catalyst.
它让你有机会重新审视人生  看清什么最重要
It got you to reevaluate. Now you know what's important.
你可以选择继续这样的人生
You can choose to hold onto that.
对吧
Right?
绝对值得一试
It's certainly worth trying.
深呼吸  不要动
Deep breath, stay very still.
让豪斯别再整什么领队的事了吧
Just tell House to drop the whole team leader thing.
这是唯一能够解决这件事的方法
That's the only way it'll go away.
我倒觉得这是个不错的想法
I don't think it's such a bad idea.
给你们部门增设结构不是坏事
A little more structure in your department couldn't hurt.
没错
Yeah.
豪斯这么做就是因为他热爱组织结构
House is doing this because of his great love of structure,
而不是因为他想让我们互相反目
not because he wants us to turn on each other.
那就别反目啊
So don't do that.
多个更有责任感的人管事
It makes sense to have someone in there
不是坏事
with a little more accountability.
只要不是亚当斯就行
As long as it's not Adams.
她把这件事视作依照她自己的蓝图
She sees the whole thing as an opportunity
重置整个部门的机会
to remake the department in her image.
也不该是朴克  理由很明显
Or park, for obvious reasons.
陶博又有孩子  可忙了
And Taub's got the kids. He's pretty busy.
你真想争取这份
Are you seriously angling for a job
我在任时你一直嘲笑的工作吗
that you mocked its fate the whole time I had it?
我没想要这个职位
I don't want the job.
你只是不想让给别人罢了
You just don't want anyone else to have it.
这下有意思了
This'll be great.
你祖母挺性感啊
Your grandmother's kind of sexy.
这是塔拉斯·舍甫琴科  伟大的乌克兰诗人
That is Taras Shevchenko, the greatest Ukrainian poet.
就是他创作的
Is he the guy behind
"旧日有朋自克列缅丘格来"吗
"There once was a man from kremenchuk"?
帮我搬这个咖啡桌
Help me move coffee table.
那我们在哪儿喝咖啡啊
Well, then where will we have coffee?
我说的咖啡是指威士忌
And by "Coffee" I mean scotch.
咖啡和酒对我来说不够真实
Coffee and booze are artificial high for me.
兴奋来源于运动
High is in exercise.
有氧操  有意思  还能塑臀
Dance aerobics. Fun, and good for the butt.
竟然听艾美·格兰特
Amy Grant?
我知道
I know.
但有个辣妹
But there's a hot girl
正在我的客厅跳来跳去  所以...
jumping up and down in my living room, so...
*没有借口*
*No exceptions*
你们只有有限的时间
You have a limited amount of time
来记住一堆没有意思的事
to learn a ton of uninteresting facts.
欢迎来到我的地盘
Welcome to my wheelhouse.
你还带了量角器来吗
You brought a protractor?
说不定要做饼状图呢
You never know when you might need to make a pie chart.
看来有人
Looks like someone
在为队长的职位献殷勤啊
is currying favor for the team leader position.
没错
Yes.
我们会运用最基本的字母记忆法
We'll be using a basic alphabet technique
再加上缩写助记
with a mnemonic multiplier.
在高中  他们叫我"背书怪物"
In high school, they called me "The bookie monster."
临时测验  你们在哪儿买的烛台
Pop quiz. Where did you get the candlesticks?
三秒倒数  一  二  三
On three. One, two, three.
-摩洛哥  -丹佛
- Morocco. - Denver.
喝了吧  今晚会很难熬的
Drink up. It's gonna be a long night.
你真的觉得这个人荷尔蒙正常后
You really think this guy's gonna hulk out
就会立刻变回去吗
once the hormones kick in?
有的雄性蜥蜴做俯卧撑来吸引异性
Some male lizards do push-ups to attract mates.
当科学家给它们注射睾酮素后
When scientists gave them extra testosterone,
它们会做俯卧撑做到死
they did push-ups until they died.
就跟你昨天能够让奇斯帮你搬一箱文件
Same drive you took advantage of to get Chase
到你车里是一样的道理
to carry a box of files down to your car yesterday.
脑室周围及皮层下的白质未见异常
Periventricular and subcortical white matter are clean.
所以你是说男子气慨
So you're saying masculinity is
是根深蒂固且毫无理性的
ingrained and irrational.
我是说这种尝试是毫无意义的...
I'm saying it's pointless to try--
引申开来  你的意思就是
By extension, you're also saying
女性特质是开明并理性的
femininity is enlightened and rational.
这是我们都应有的状态
It's the way we should all be,
男人只是做不到而已
guys just are incapable of it.
脑干和脊髓未见异常
Brain stem and cord are clean.
我抓抓鼻子行吗
Is it okay if I scratch my nose?
请便
Go ahead.
看来他没得多发性硬化
Guess he doesn't have M.S.
不对劲
Something's wrong.
是你手的问题吗
Is it your hand?
不  是我的眼睛
No, it's my eyes.
我看到重影了
I'm--I'm seeing double.
笑一个  这是你们的蜜月旅行
Smile. It's your honeymoon.
除去别的症状  是什么导致了复视
So what causes double vision on top of all the other symptoms?
肯定不是脑部肿瘤  否则扫描就能看到
It's not a brain tumor or we would've seen it on the scans.
眼睛检查也没发现异样
Eye exam didn't offer anything conclusive.
我们来拍点冬天的照片吧
Let's do some winter shots.
换装
Wardrobe change.
甲状腺疾病相关眼病合并肌无力
Thyroid eye disease in conjunction with graves.
甲状腺功能正常
Thyroid level was normal.
看看这个
Check it out.
辛普森拿这个
Simpson traded this in exchange
换我在休息的抽空帮他
for me helping out on some of my days off.
是主观能动性和领导能力的不错体现啊
Quite the display of initiative and leadership.
你那么聪明是不会被这么露骨的贿赂买通的
But you're way too smart to fall for a blatant bribe like that.
或是明晃晃地事业线秀
Or a blatant flaunting of cleavage.
比如那个
Like those.
说好的不让豪斯离间我们呢
What happened to not letting House get to you?
你们就跟旅鼠一样
You're like lemmings,
排着队的要接受羞辱的洗礼
marching off the cliff of competitive humiliation.
我只是在做我的本职工作
All I'm doing is my job.
豪斯表示过他觉得我很有魅力
House has indicated that he considers me attractive.
利用自身优势
There's nothing wrong with me
来提升自己  何错之有
using my strengths to my advantage.
这么说来
With an argument like that,
你要不就跪下...
maybe you should just drop down to your knees and--
除非这不是你的优势
I mean, unless that's not your strength.
抱一个吧  大个子  外面好冷啊
Oh, big hug, big man. It's cold out here.
冒着扰乱这个高效的拍照活动
At the risk of derailing this
和你们争相挖苦的会议的风险
very productive photo shoot and bickering session,
会不会是重症肌无力呢
what about myasthenia gravis?
眼外肌无力导致复视
Extra-ocular muscle weakness leads to double vision,
膀胱的肌无力导致尿失禁
atonic bladder leads to incontinence.
可能在睾酮素很低时被触发
Could've been triggered when his T got really low.
那个小个子
Ooh, a little one.
他是个不错人选
He'd be a good pick.
漂亮
Smooth.
你让其他人相互竞争
You let the rest of them compete,
鹬蚌相争  渔翁得利啊
tear each other to pieces, then you swoop in with a save.
开始用免疫球蛋白  血浆置换
Start the patient on ivig and plasmapheresis.
你能来做这个吗
Can you handle that, please?
-我要和你谈谈  -那抓紧时间
- I need a minute. - Well, make it quick.
我们要拍在孟菲斯的照片了
We're doin' Memphis.
你觉得你想要这样  但这其实是个糟糕的主意
You think you want this, but it's a bad idea.
我本来想做多莉山主题公园主题的
I was gonna go Dollywood,
但我想那假发不适合我
but I'm not sure I could pull off that wig.
本来每个人都相处融洽
Everybody was playing nice,
在你的世界里  融洽却无法解决病例
and in your world, nice doesn't solve cases,
但在那件事发生后
but after what happened,
有几分团结也是好事
a little bonding is a good thing.
我们仍就有想法  各执一词
We still have ideas, we still argue.
可能当我们相互欣赏时  能更好得协作
Maybe it could work better if we appreciate each other.
精彩的演说
That was impressive.
你说这番话时怎么嘴皮子都没动一下
You said that whole thing without once moving your lips.
你不能动的那里
The ones you're not moving.
我明白了
Oh. I get it.
我不参与你这愚蠢的游戏
I won't play along with your stupid games,
所以我就不是男人了
so I'm no longer a man.
聪明
Clever.
事实上  你不愿意参与我这愚蠢的游戏
Actually, you won't play along with my stupid games
是因为你已经不是男人了
because you're no longer a man.
尽管还很聪明
Still clever, though.
研究表明抚养孩子
Studies have shown that raising kids
会降低睾酮素水平
lowers testosterone levels in men.
你投入越多激素水平就越低
The more involved you are, the lower it gets.
没错  有了孩子让我变中性了
Right. Having kids has neutered me.
又或者正因如此我才成熟了
Or maybe it's helped me finally grow up.
感觉如何
How are you feeling?
只要我把眼睛闭起来就挺好
As long as I keep my eyes closed, pretty good.
应该说是相当不错
Really good, actually.
我充满活力  感觉自信  头脑清晰
I got energy, I feel confident, clear.
睾酮素确实会让你振作起来
Testosterone does tend to perk you up.
亲爱的  我给你买了汉堡
Hey, hon. I brought you a burger.
是吗
Really?
你住院了  想吃什么吃什么
You're in the hospital. Eat whatever you want.
你是世上最好的老婆
You're the best wife ever.
我这么说
And I'm not just saying that
不只因为你牛仔裤下的翘臀如此性感
because of how great your ass looks in those jeans.
不好意思  我只是...
I'm sorry. That was--
没关系
No, it's okay.
女人们都喜欢知道自己有魅力
Girl likes to know she's appreciated.
过来
Come here.
我认为我们应该和高层们
So I think we should talk to leading lights
聊聊讲座和DVD的事了
about seminars and DVDs.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你一直都挺犹豫的
You were worried about the commitment.
没错  不过做生意没理由半途而废嘛
Yeah, there's no point in being in business with them halfway.
你觉得可以吗
You okay with that?
我很高兴你终于下定决心了
It's good to finally have a decision.
好的
Okay.
费帝尔是最让她操心的弟弟
Fedir is the brother she worries about the most.
自从路巴去世以后
Ever since Luba passed.
不好意思
Sorry.
不过这是我们能找到的
But this is the closest we could find
最像冰冷无情政府办公室的地方了
to the cold, soulless offices of a government bureaucracy.
如果你不用你的办公室  我去用
If you're not using your office, I will.
多米尼卡和她的高中朋友还有联系吗
Does Dominika still communicate with her high school friends?
维斯莉  还有
Uh, Vasyl, yes.
奥克萨娜就没有了 自从她亲了帕傅洛后就断了
Oksana, no. Not since she kissed Pavlo.
因为那贱人知道多米尼卡也喜欢他
'cause that bitch knew that Dominika liked him.
不对
Wrong.
奥克萨娜是个荡妇  我跟她绝交了
Oh, Oksana is a slut. Dead to me.
正确的答案反而是错误的答案
The right answer is the wrong answer.
不会有丈夫对妻子朋友的
No husband would pay that much attention
八卦如此感兴趣的
to his wife's friend dramas.
你不是已经离过三次婚了吗
Haven't you been divorced three times?
在几次离婚中间  我的婚龄  照实算
In-between those divorces, I was married, non-fraudulently,
已经十二年了
for 12 years total,
比屋里所有人都要长12年
which is 12 years longer than anyone in this room.
让开
Move.
你也打算去争取组长的位置吗
So are you going for this team leader thing?
也许
Probably.
你应得的
You deserve it.
你比我经验多得多
You have way more experience than me.
你要放弃吗
You're giving up?
我想要那职位
I wish.
我还有医学院的贷款要还
I still have a lot of med school debt,
我父母的房屋抵押贷款也许要我帮忙
and my parents need help with their mortgage.
因此我急需用钱
So I could kinda use the money.
过去一小时所有东西我都只能看到一个了
As of an hour ago, I'm just seeing one of everything.
看来你们猜对了...
Looks like you guys were right--
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
我急需用钱
"I could use the money"?
想要耍我的话  得演得再像点
You want to game me, you gotta do better than that.
-奇斯  -你要是想当组长
- Chase-- - You want to be a leader,
就要知道如何操纵他人
you have to know how to manipulate.
你不能轻易泄露...
You can't just spill--
我觉得他的眼白是黄色的
I think the whites of his eyes were yellow.
一切还好吧
Everything okay?
黄疸
Jaundice.
你的肝脏有问题
There's something wrong with your liver.
肝功能检测确定了他的酶指标
Liver function tests confirm his enzymes
完全是一团糟
are totally out of whack.
那么肯定不是重症肌无力了
So much for myasthenia gravis.
我们能快点吗
Can we hurry this up?
我中午还有个政府官员要去骗
I have a government to defraud at noon.
如果有必要  你应该马上走
If you need to leave, you should.
我有足够理由相信我们的病人患的是结节病
I'm fairly confident our patient's got sarcoidosis.
你说的话很有权威的感觉
Wow, you said that with so much authority.
有没有人瑟瑟发抖啦
Did anyone else get chills?
不过我发现病人
Just until I realized our patient has
没有肺实质病变的迹象
no sign of parenchymal lung abnormalities,
说明结节病可能性不大
which makes sarcoidosis a long shot.
照搬书本也没比露乳有用
And bookkeeping isn't gonna get you any farther than boobs.
客观来说  春光确实很有帮助
Though in fairness, the boobs were really, really helping.
我还认为是重症肌无力
I still think it's myasthenia gravis.
你是不是忘记刚才的总结了
Did you miss the recap?
我们对那进行了治疗  出现了肝损伤
We treated for that. The liver tanked.
但他的视觉恢复了
But his vision got better.
肝脏问题可能是乳糜泻的标志
Liver problems could be a sign of celiac.
住院以来他又开始吃麸质了
He's been back on gluten since he's been in the hospital.
昨天他还吃了个汉堡
Yesterday he had a burger.
这可能使乳糜泻变成导火索
That would've kicked the celiac into gear,
从而导致肝脏问题
causing the liver problems.
那你的理论是他得了两种不相干的病
So your theory is that he has two unrelated diseases.
而同时他的睾酮素水平还过低
And he's already got low testosterone.
我好想记得豪斯很讨厌这种巧合
I seem to remember something about House hating coincidences.
没错
It's true.
我认为是莱姆病
I think it's Lyme disease.
只得了一种病叫做莱姆
One single disease named "Lyme."
没有起皮疹
Without a rash.
这种病有百分之十的患者不起皮疹
10% of cases present without a rash.
那就是莱姆病
Lyme disease it is.
给病人用抗生素
Start the patient on antibiotics.
现在我得赶紧回家以防我的假妻子真生气
Now I have to get home before my fake wife gets real annoyed.
有什么事困扰你吗
Something bothering you?
我让护士去再拿个枕头
I asked the nurse for an extra pillow.
已经半小时过去了
That was half an hour ago.
不好意思
Sorry.
这的事有点多
Things can get pretty hectic.
只是个枕头而已
It was a pillow.
我是说  拿个枕头能有多难...
I mean, how hard can a pil--
听听看  我就像个混蛋
Listen to me. I'm being a jerk.
睾酮素会使你脾气变差
Testosterone can give you a shorter temper
就算你没病也是如此
even when you're not sick.
你注意到了并做出了调整  这很好
You noticed and adjusted. That's a good thing.
刚接到我们律师的电话
Just got a call from our lawyer.
你更改了我们给高管们的报价
You changed our counter to leading lights?
在第二任期你理应获得
You deserve proper billing
合适的收入和工资增长
and a salary bump in the second term.
我们聊过这个问题了
We talked about this.
我们认为冒着破坏交易的风险不值得
We decided it wasn't worth potentially blowing the deal.
没事的
It'll be fine.
我还有些工作要做
I've got to get some work done.
这些是你每周五给我买的鲜花
These are such pretty flowers you buy for me
每次都从爱迪生街和康韦街交口处
every Friday, from Japanese florist,
的日本花店里买
on corner of Edison and Conway.
还差一件事
Just one more thing.
带上这戒指  我们就是夫妻了
With this ring, I thee wedded.
你和男友突然离开时把它落在这里了
You left it here when you skipped town with your boyfriend.
你一直留着戒指
You kept the rings.
实际上  我试图用它和
Actually, I tried to trade them to a hooker
一个妓女做笔交易
for unspecified favors,
但结果发现她不收锌制品
but it turns out she doesn't accept zinc.
就像现代童话似的
Like modern fairytale.
格利高里·豪斯夫妇吗
Dr. and Mrs. Gregory House?
没错
Yeah.
内特·魏曼  美国移民局
Nate Weinmann. U.S. Immigration.
欢迎到我们家来
Welcome to our home.
给他点时间
Give him time.
我十四岁时
When I was 14,
有个我想追的女孩
there was a girl I wanted to impress,
我跳到她家的屋顶
so I jumped off the roof of her house.
结果扭到了脚
Broke my ankle.
乔基本上算是在经历青春期
Joe's basically going through puberty.
需要一段时间进行调整
It'll take him a while to adjust.
我看了一个乔以前
I-I tracked down a video
进行经商培训的演讲
from one of Joe's business coaching seminars
是在我认识他以前的
from before I knew him.
最近常听人谈论妥协的价值
I'm hearing a lot about the value of compromise.
可我们并不生活在《芝麻街》
We don't live on Sesame Street.
我们生活在现实世界中  这是一个生意场
We live in the real world, the business world.
不能成王  即为败寇
If you're not a winner, you're a loser.
如果你无法接受这样的事实
If you aren't comfortable with that,
就回家种田去吧
go open a pottery studio.
我永远不会和视频中的这类男人约会
I never would have gone out with the guy in this video.
你记得她最后一次见维斯莉是什么时候吗
Uh, do you remember the last time she visited Vasyl?
我想下  应该是...
Uh, let me see, that would be...
是八月吧
August?
不对  是七月
No. No, July.
因为我记得正好是在我们半周年纪念日之后
'Cause I remember it was right after our half-anniversary,
我还忘记在她的旅行箱中藏礼物了
and I forgot to put a gift in her suitcase.
之后她总是对此耿耿于怀
And...I've never heard the end of that one.
豪斯家特制
House specialty.
我想出来的双关
I made up this pun.
这个是
Is it...
谢谢
Thank you.
亲爱的  你干嘛难为我啊
Honey, why do you do this to me?
明知道我要控制体重
You know I'm watching my weight.
那你可以不要半夜起来
Then maybe you'll stop eating cheese
开冰箱偷吃奶酪啊
in front of open fridge in middle of the night.
这真好吃
This is delicious.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们这里看上去很不错
So everything looks good in here.
我只要再找个邻居
I'm just gonna step out and get a corroborating interview
确认下你们的情况就可以了
from one of the neighbors.
邻居
Neighbors?
这大白天的
It's... it's middle of the day.
我想别人都在工作吧
I-I-I think everybody's at work.
那我就如实写上去
Yeah, then they're at work.
我就需要在表格上打几个钩
I just got a form to check off,
你很有希望获得永久居住权
and you will be on your way to permanent status.
先生  打扰了
Excuse me, sir.
你有空吗
Do you have a minute?
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
你认识豪斯医生和他夫人吗
Do you know Dr. And Mrs. House?
当然  我和他们做了
Of course, they've been my neighbors
两年的邻居了
about two years, now.
他俩人很好
Lovely couple.
几乎每天晚上都能见到他们
I see them almost every night.
小两口如胶似漆的
They seem always to be together.
好的  谢谢你
Great, well, thanks for your help.
再见
Cheerio.
你在我家门口偷偷摸摸干嘛
Hey, what're you doing? That's my door.
我在为新开的中餐馆发广告
Handing out menus for a new Chinese place.
你就是那个每周六晚上
You're that guy that plays noisy video games
和豪斯一起玩电子游戏的人  吵死了
with House on Saturday nights.
我的解释很简单
There's a simple explanation.
明早十点到我办公室来
Be at my office tomorrow at 10:00.
病人不见一丝好转
The patient's shown zero improvement.
因为他才用了一个晚上的抗生素
Because he's only been on the antibiotics overnight.
也可能他得的不是莱姆病
Or because he doesn't have Lyme disease.
你人在哪里
Where are you?
没事瞎转悠
Oh, just chillin'.
我在美国移民局
U.S. Citizenship at Immigration.
和我老婆与律师一起就移民诈骗等待谈话呢
Waiting on my fraud interview with my wife and my attorney.
-没啥大事儿  -豪斯
- No big. - House.
别打电话了
Hang up.
我还是觉得病人得的是重症肌无力和乳糜泻
I still think it's myasthenia gravis plus celiac.
他的饮食结构变化有很大的影响
His change in diet has to be significant.
只需要做一个肠道活检就能确诊
We just need to do an intestinal biopsy to confirm.
介于他血小板计数低
With his low platelet count,
做活检可能会
a biopsy puts him at risk
引起腹腔出血  危及生命
for an abdominal bleed, which puts him at risk of death.
你别再打了
Either you're done,
否则我不陪你进去
or you're walking in there without a lawyer.
懂了  这听上去像电话铃
I know, it sounds like a phone,
其实是为开会前提醒我撒尿设的闹铃
but it's a timer to remind me to pee before our meeting.
你好  老伙计
Hello, old chap.
你要自救啊
You need to save yourself.
我昨晚一夜未眠
I was up last night
想找个新的托辞  可是找不到
trying to find another angle, but I can't.
就和移民局的人说  你和多米尼卡相爱过
Tell immigration you were in love with Dominika,
但是你们的婚姻破碎了
but your marriage fell apart,
所以才一直分居
and that's why you haven't been living together.
她会被永久驱逐的
She'll be deported permanently.
豪斯  我知道你喜欢多米尼卡
House, I know you like Dominika,
你和她一起很开心  但是你被人逮到了
you have fun with her, but you got caught.
除此之外  别无他法
There's no getting out of this.
你不回监狱就是最好的结果了
The best you could hope for is that you don't go back to jail.
让我的小组  别做活检
Tell my team to... to skip the biopsy
继续用抗生素
and give the antibiotics more time.
轮到我们了
They're ready for us.
我表明了立场  获得了胜利
I drew a line in the sand, and I won.
我们应该庆祝胜利
We should be celebrating.
要再给你们几分钟时间吗
Do you need a few minutes?
是的  我感觉好多了
You're right. I keep getting better.
就这样了
That's just it.
你是赢了
You won.
你提出的要求可能会使交易泡汤
You made a demand that could've blown up the deal,
而且你也没征询过我的意见
and you never even asked me.
交易没有泡汤  他们妥协了
Deal didn't blow up. They caved.
乔  是你在研讨会上说的
Joe, you say it in your seminars.
过程与结果同样重要
Process matters just as much as results.
你就因为我在这件小事上没和你商量
Are you seriously busting my chops
所以就给我脸色看吗
because I made one little move without you?
你就不能闪一边去  让我
How 'bout stepping aside and letting me
像个男人那样做次主不行吗
be the man in this relationship for a change?
你现在真是不可理喻
I really can't talk to you right now.
我不知道怎么会说出这种话
I don't know why I said that.
就感觉非常生气
Just I got so angry.
希望这次的药用完
Hopefully after this dose,
你的情况能好转  可以出院回家
you'll start to feel better, and we can get you home.
我还有个检查想做
But I'd like to do one more test.
不能仅凭一个近视的愤怒邻居的证词
The testimony of one angry, nearsighted neighbor
就无视其它的证据吧
shouldn't outweigh all other evidence.
有照片  水电煤的账单...
Photos, utility bills...
搞得好像你的委托人从没造过假似的
Yes, because your clients would never fake anything.
我们承认假扮邻居是个错误
Uh, we acknowledge the neighbor thing was a mistake,
但并不是说所有其他的证明
but that doesn't mean that all of the other documentation
就是一纸空文了
should just be thrown out.
听着  我知道你是出于本职工作
Look, look, you know, I get that it's your job
竭尽全力想要立案  但是请你闭嘴
to try to act like there's a case here, but shut up.
好的
Okay.
美国公民及移民服务局将会
USCIS will be denying
拒绝佩特洛娃小姐的绿卡申请
Miss Petrova's green card application.
你会被转去移民庭
You'll be referred to immigration court
准备离境手续
for deportation proceedings.
同时  我们会把你诈骗的事实
And we're gonna inform your parole officer
告知你的假释官
about evidence of fraud.
所以  如果没有人还要补充的话...
So unless anybody has anything else to add...
我求你了  别把他送回监狱
Please, I am begging, do not send him back to jail.
或许我们没有共同生活过...
Maybe we have not lived together all these...
豪斯夫人  我建议你别说下去了
Mrs. House, I have to advise you not to continue.
我和这个男人
This man and I,
我们的结合是因为爱情吗
did we marry for love?
不是
No.
但是在过去的一周里
But this past week,
我们过得非常快乐
we have a lot of fun.
为了欺骗美国政府我们真是挤尽脑汁啊  是不是
Working really hard to fool the U.S. Government, right?
别回答她
Don't answer that.
你说晚了
Way ahead of you.
我们的婚姻是虚假的
It was fake, but...
但是这感觉却是真实的
It felt real.
或许是因为这婚姻开始变得真实了
Maybe because it become real.
这个男人
This man...
我丈夫
My husband.
我想要和他共同生活  但是如果做不到
I want to stay with him, but if I cannot,
请你们把我送走  给他自由吧
please send me away, and let him be free.
我爱他
I love him.
你说的我一个字都不信
I didn't buy a word you said.
但是法官可能信
But a judge might.
我让你留下
I'm gonna let you stay.
但是在未来六个月里
But for the next six months,
我不会忘了你们这事儿
I'm gonna hold onto this file.
无论凌晨还是深夜
And our investigators are gonna show up unannounced
我们的调查员都可能突然到访
6:00 a.m., 11:00 at night, and they better find
最好让他们看到你们俩坐在沙发上
the two of you sitting on the couch watching NCIS
看看电视  吃吃冰激凌  亲密无间
eating ice cream from the same spoon.
否则你们两个都别想
Or both of you will be sent to places
再过现在这样的好日子
far less pleasant than New Jersey.
你前面说的...
What you just said in there...
别担心
Don't worry.
我聪明得很  才不会爱上你
I'm much too smart to be falling in love with you.
卫生间里给我加个置物架
I will be needing extra shelf in bathroom.
腹腔活检发现小肠绒毛扁平
Abdominal biopsy showed flattened villi.
看来你关于乳糜泻的推测是对的
Looks like you were right about celiac.
奇斯违背豪斯安排活检被刺了一刀
You do remember Chase got stabbed
这事你没忘吧
doing a test House didn't order?
类比得当  因为两位病人
Good comparison, since both patients
都被类固醇折磨得不行
were tweaked on steroids.
你这样做不过是为了盖过奇斯和朴克的风头
You only did this to score points over Chase and Park.
我们猜对了
We were right.
我证明了  病人也没有大出血
I proved it, and the patient didn't bleed out.
你为什么揪住这事不放
Why are you being a jerk about this?
我们去看看豪斯回来没有
Let's go see if House is back.
病人出现呼吸困难
Patient's having trouble breathing.
那就不是乳糜泻了
So much for celiac.
呼吸已经平稳
His breathing is stabilized,
可是肺功能只有60%  而且肝脏积水
but his lung function is at 60%, and his liver is tanking.
还具有乳糜泻的主要症状
And he has major symptoms of celiac
但是没有患乳糜泻
without actually having celiac.
可能是惠普尔氏病
Could be Whipple's.
不能解释失禁
Doesn't explain the incontinence.
小肠淋巴瘤呢
Intestinal lymphoma?
不能解释视物重影
Doesn't explain the double vision.
随时欢迎加入讨论
Any time you want to jump in.
真有有氧操这种东西吗
Is Dance Aerobics even a thing?
有助美臀
It's good for the butt.
会不会是寄生虫感染
What about a parasitic infection?
类圆线虫属寄生虫感染能破坏小肠
Strongyloides is known to damage the small intestine.
在美国感染线虫跟中彩差不多是一个几率
In this country, he's about as likely to get that as win powerball.
总有人中彩嘛  每周都有
Someone does win powerball. Every week.
病人数月前去过波多黎各
The patient went to Puerto Rico a few months ago.
美国少数几个有可能感染线虫
One of the few places in the U.S.
的地区之一
you could pick up strongyloides.
治疗需用伊维菌素
Treatment is ivermectin.
此药用于肝功能障碍患者
We give that to someone with liver problems,
可能导致他癫痫发作  甚至更糟
he could have seizures, or worse.
治吧
Do it.
最近常听人谈论妥协的价值
I'm hearing a lot about the value of compromise.
可我们并不生活在《芝麻街》
But we don't live on Sesame Street,
我们生活在现实...
we live in the real--
我在想我们或许是忽略了某种病征
I was wondering if maybe we overlooked a symptom,
或者别的什么
or something.
非常有道理
Makes perfect sense.
比如我们忽略了你的娘娘腔症状
If you're the patient, and "pantywaist" is the symptom.
我和亚当斯都认为病人可能患有乳糜泻
Adams and I both thought the patient could have celiac,
可是她甘冒奇险  做了活检
but only she was willing to go out on a limb and run the test.
我放弃
I gave up.
所以你在这里看励志演讲
Now you're in here watching a motivational speech.
连你试图重拾自信的方法都缺乏自信
Even your attempt to get your balls back lacks balls.
世界中  这是一个生意场
--world, the business world.
不能成王  即为败寇
If you're not a winner, you're a loser.
他的声音  比现在要低沉
His voice--it's lower than it is now.
职业演说家的声音
If only there was a good reason
为什么会嘶哑  真是个问题
for a professional speaker to be hoarse.
回家种田去吧
Go open a pottery studio.
有道理
Good point.
不是有道理  是真知灼见
It's not a good point. It's a decent point.
你又犯了  还有别的视频吗
You're doing it again. You have any other videos?
演讲片段
Other seminars?
有几段
A couple.
发现弱点的时候
When you see a weakness,
就是拿出勇气的时候
that's a time for strength.
许多人会说  "我很生气
A lot of people say, "Oh, I feel bad about it.
是旁人犯了错"
The other guy made a mistake."
你过早放弃了自己的观点
You bailed too early.
现在功劳是我一个人的了
Now I get all the credit.
慢性声音嘶哑
Chronic hoarseness
是一种病的症状
is a symptom of a condition called
静息性甲状腺炎
Silent thyroiditis.
-可是我没有声音嘶哑  -没错
- But I'm not hoarse. - Exactly.
可你三年前声音嘶哑
But you were three years ago.
静息性甲状腺炎出现又消失
Silent thyroiditis comes and goes.
此病正是另一病症的症状
And it, in turn, is a symptom
多腺体自身免疫综合征3型
of polyglandular autoimmune syndrome type 3,
所以注射类固醇实在要不得
Which makes this a really bad idea.
病症攻击自身的内分泌系统
Pas 3 attacks the body's own endocrine system,
接二连三地破坏腺体
moving from gland to gland.
从甲状腺开始
It started in the thyroid,
而且很可能由于你睾酮素水平低的原因
and probably helped along by your low testosterone,
轻易影响到内脏
moved on to the gut.
造成了乳糜泻
Where it caused celiac disease,
或者说  如果你摄入麸质  会造成乳糜泻
or it would've if you weren't on a gluten-free diet.
我是对的
I was right.
真是相当有用的线索
This is incredibly relevant.
随着时间推进  病症侵害你的胸腺
Eventually, pas 3 attacked your thymus gland.
造成重症肌无力  终于导致你入院
You developed myasthenia gravis, which landed you in here,
而你又开始吃麸质  让病情变得更糟
And you started eating gluten, which only made things worse.
我会好起来吧
So am I gonna be okay?
我们会用大剂量类固醇
We'll treat the various conditions
治疗各种症状
with high-dose steroids.
如果有效  你就没事了
Assuming they respond, you should be fine.
那睾酮素呢
And the testosterone?
蛋被踢了就是被踢了
Kicked in the nuts is kicked in the nuts.
过去的一周里
Over the past week,
你们都有得意之时  也有失意之刻
you've all had good moments and bad.
竞选者中无一胜出
No one candidate has prevailed.
所以现在  我们开展竞赛
And so now, we embark upon a contest
考验医术  耐心和技巧
of medical strength, stamina, and skill.
能不能跳过这段
Can we just get this over with?
如果澳大利亚代表
If the competitor representing Australia
有意主动扣掉一分
would like to take a point deduction,
他大可以继续嘀咕
he should, by all means, continue yapping.
你得意的样子快让我们觉得
Your glee is on the verge of making this
不值得继续下去了
not worth it for any of us.
至少让我点燃火炬吧
Can I at least light the torch?
快点
Hurry.
我宣布  第一项
I declare open the games
第二项  比赛开始
of the number one, number two competition.
我宣布
Je declare ouvert--
好了  各就各位  预备  缝合
All right. Ready, set, suture!
打针了
T time.
如果我不注射会怎样
What happens if I don't take it?
或者降低剂量
Or at least go to a much lower dose?
出现副作用了吗
Are you having side effects?
没有  我感觉很好  更敏捷  更清晰
No, I feel great. Faster, clearer.
更像我自己
More like myself.
可是我的婚姻和事业
But my marriage and my career,
都建立在我处于另一状态的基础上
they're both built on me being somebody else.
睾酮水平低可能导致抑郁
Low testosterone can cause depression
和睡眠问题
and problems sleeping.
而且与骨质疏松症和糖尿病
It's also been linked to conditions
等病症有关联
such as osteoporosis and diabetes.
会让你的生活变得困难而危险
It'll make your life harder and more dangerous
更何况你还要服用许多药物
on top of all the meds you'll be taking.
我愿意冒这个险
I'll take that risk.
没有它的我更好
I'm a better man without it.
的确为诊断科增添许多色彩
Well, this certainly has brought more structure to the department.
真的吗  我只对轮椅赛跑感兴趣
Really, I'm just excited for the wheelchair race.
你退出得很聪明
You were smart not to enter.
不参与  就不会输
Never in, never lose.
再说你也没什么骨气
And since you no longer have stones.
在工作中  stones常指一个人的特质  比如好好先生
在此豪斯又借以强调陶博娘娘腔
我帮你分担那每周50小时
I'll split the 50 a week with you.
成交
Deal.
亲爱的  我回来了
Honey, I'm home!